<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pDiem on Phala Network Wiki</title>
    <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/pdiem/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pDiem on Phala Network Wiki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/pdiem/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Local Testnet</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/pdiem/deploy-local-testnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/pdiem/deploy-local-testnet/</guid>
      <description>There are two options to run the pdiem demo:
 Use our Docker Compose file Build from the source and run it directly  This guide will only cover the Docker Compose approach because it handles everything automatically for you. It installs the dependencies, builds the code, starts the network with the components connected correctly, and start them.
In the development environment we build the code natively. The pro users who want to hack on our code can look into the Dockerfiles and docker-compose file to learn how the system is configured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play with pDiem</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/pdiem/play-with-pdiem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/pdiem/play-with-pdiem/</guid>
      <description>The pdiem full stack includes:
 A local Diem testnet: diem, diem-cli A Phala Network local testnet with the pdiem contract: phala-node, phala-pruntime, phala-phost A relayer to connect the both networks: pdiem-relayer  With the pdiem full stack running, we are going to send some Diem transactions to the pdiem deposit account, and check if the pdiem contract has received it.
Create Diem accounts First, start the diem-cli from the same directory:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reservation-based Model</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/pdiem/reservation-based-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/pdiem/reservation-based-model/</guid>
      <description>A bridge connects the local blockchain to a remote blockchain. pDiem follows the &amp;quot;reservation asset&amp;quot; cross-chain asset transferring pattern (see the equivalent pattern defined in XCM Format). In our case, pDiem (and its parachain) is the local blockchain, and Diem is the remote blockchain.
The pDiem bridge controls a set of sovereign accounts (see XCM Format - Definitions) on the Diem side, which hold all the Diem assets transferred to pDiem side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Light Validation Client</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/pdiem/light-validation-client/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/pdiem/light-validation-client/</guid>
      <description>The Basics A minimal cross-chain bridge can transfer assets between the two blockchains. In the reservation-based model, it requires that the local blockchain can confirm some deposit to its sovereign accounts, and the remote blockchain can confirm the withdraw commands from the local blockchain. The validation of the blockchain is done by full nodes, but they are too heavy to fit into a smart contract or blockchain, in terms of the computation and the storage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contract Implementation</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/pdiem/contract-implementation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/pdiem/contract-implementation/</guid>
      <description>WIP</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Relayer</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/pdiem/the-relayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/pdiem/the-relayer/</guid>
      <description>WIP</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future Works</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/pdiem/future-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/pdiem/future-works/</guid>
      <description>WIP</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
