<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>User Guides on Phala Network Wiki</title>
    <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/khala-user/</link>
    <description>Recent content in User Guides on Phala Network Wiki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/khala-user/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Polkadot{.js} Extension Guide</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/khala-user/polkadot-js-extension/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/khala-user/polkadot-js-extension/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, we present how to use Polkadot{.js} Extension to create/import Khala account. Khala Network, as the parachain of Kusama, shares the accounts of Kusama Relay Chain.
Install Polkadot{.js} Extension   Get extension from https://polkadot.js.org/extension/
  Choose Chrome or Firefox Extension according to your explorer
  Create New Account  Choose your installed Polkadot{.js} Extension; Click &amp;ldquo;+&amp;rdquo;, and choose &amp;ldquo;Create new account&amp;rdquo;;  Keep mnemonic seed safe; Choose Network &amp;ldquo;Allow use on any chain&amp;rdquo;, fill in the descriptive name and password, and click &amp;ldquo;Add the account with the generated seed&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guidance of Delegation StakePool</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/khala-user/stake-pool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/khala-user/stake-pool/</guid>
      <description>Delegator Token holders (i.e. delegators) can obtain mining rewards by delegating PHA to the StakePool, which can be understood as &amp;ldquo;depositing to earn interest&amp;rdquo;. This guide will introduce how to earn rewards through delegation in Phala Network.
How to Delegate Introduction of Delegation Phala Network’s protocol allows token holders to delegate PHA into StakePool. The owner of the StakePool uses the PHA to mine and stake. The mining rewards will be distributed to the delegators according to the delegation share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set Up Identity</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/khala-user/set-up-identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/khala-user/set-up-identity/</guid>
      <description>Phala Network provides a naming system that allows participants to add personal information to their on-chain account and subsequently ask for verification of this information by registrars.
After your identity is added, it can be used in many applications in Phala or Khala ecosystem. For example, in Secure Worker mining, this will help you attracting delegators to trust and vote for you.
Setting an Identity Users can set an identity by registering through default fields such as legal name, display name, website, Twitter handle, Riot handle, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
