<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Phala Network Wiki</title>
    <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Phala Network Wiki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 01:16:05 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Run a Local Development Network</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/run-a-local-development-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/run-a-local-development-network/</guid>
      <description>Basic understanding of Linux shell and compiling is necessary to follow this tutorial.
 Overview In this tutorial, we are going to set up a &amp;quot;Hello World&amp;quot; development environment. We are gonig to deploy a full stack of the core blockchain and connect the Web UI to the blockchain. By the end of the tutorial, you will be able to:
 Send confidential transactions Get a ready-to-hack version of Phala Network for building your own confidential Dapps  A full Phala Network stack has three components plus a Web UI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World: your first confidential contract</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/your-first-confidential-contract/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/your-first-confidential-contract/</guid>
      <description>Basic understanding of Rust lanugage programming and smart contract development knowledge is necessary to follow this tutorial.
 Overview In this tutorial, we are going to continue on the development environment we have set up in the previous chapter, and explore how a confidential smart contract is made. By the end of this tutorial, you will:
 Learn how to develop a confidential contract Interact with the contract from the Web UI Build your own confidental contract  For a high-level overview of Phala Network, please check the previous chapters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description>phala-blockchain Probelm: &amp;quot;consider giving accuracy a type&amp;quot; when building substrate error[E0282]: type annotations needed --&amp;gt; .../substrate/primitives/arithmetic/src/fixed_point.rs:541:9 | 541 | let accuracy = P::ACCURACY.saturated_into(); | ^^^^^^^^ consider giving `accuracy` a type ... 1604 | / implement_fixed!( 1605 | | FixedI128, 1606 | | test_fixed_i128, 1607 | | i128, ... | 1611 | | [-170141183460469231731.687303715884105728, 170141183460469231731.687303715884105727]_&amp;quot;, 1612 | | ); | |__- in this macro invocation | = note: this error originates in a macro (in Nightly builds, run with -Z macro-backtrace for more info) This is a known issue caused by rust nightly regression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run a Gatekeeper</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc2/run-a-gatekeeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 01:16:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc2/run-a-gatekeeper/</guid>
      <description>This guide will instruct you how to set up a validator node on the Phala Network.
Preliminaries Running a Gatekeeper on a live network is a lot of responsibility! You will be accountable for not only your own stake, but also the stake of your current nominators. If you make a mistake and get slashed, your money and your reputation will be at risk. However, running a Gatekeeper can also be very rewarding, knowing that you contribute to the security of a decentralized network while growing your stash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run a full node</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc2/run-a-full-node/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 22:30:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc2/run-a-full-node/</guid>
      <description>If you&#39;re building dapps or products on a Phala Network, you probably want the ability to run a node-as-a-back-end. After all, it&#39;s always better to rely on your own infrastructure than on a third-party-hosted one in this brave new decentralized world.
This guide will show you how to connect to Phala Network PoC-2. First, let&#39;s clarify the term full node.
Types of Nodes A blockchain&#39;s growth comes from a genesis block, extrinsics, and events.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
