<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Phala Network Wiki</title>
    <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Phala Network Wiki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 01:16:05 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Run a Gatekeeper</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/gatekeeper/run-a-gatekeeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 01:16:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/gatekeeper/run-a-gatekeeper/</guid>
      <description>Setup Environment   Hardware
 CPU: 6th generation or newer Intel Core/Pentium/Celeron/Atom series. Memory: 2GB - 8GB. 2GB is indeed the minimum memory you should operate your Gatekeeper with. For better performance, you can bump it up to 4GB or 8GB, but memory more than that is unnecessary. In order to compile the binary yourself, you will need around 8GB memory. Mainboard: SGX-supported mainboard, and newer mainboards can support more SGX features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run a full node</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc2/run-a-full-node/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 22:30:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc2/run-a-full-node/</guid>
      <description>If you&#39;re building dapps or products on a Phala Network, you probably want the ability to run a node-as-a-back-end. After all, it&#39;s always better to rely on your own infrastructure than on a third-party-hosted one in this brave new decentralized world.
This guide will show you how to connect to Phala Network PoC-2. First, let&#39;s clarify the term full node.
Types of Nodes A blockchain&#39;s growth comes from a genesis block, extrinsics, and events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.1 Hardware Requirement and Configuration</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/1-1-hardware-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/1-1-hardware-configuration/</guid>
      <description>Phala Network operates on trusted hardwares, in this case, Intel CPUs which support SGX feature. SGX was first introduced in 2015 with the sixth generation Intel Core microprocessors based on the Skylake microarchitecture. In practice, the support of SGX feature also relies on your motherboard and BIOS configurations. In this section, we will first ensure that necessary hardware requirements are satisfied and all your hardwares are correcly configured.
General Hardware Requirements CPU Requirement You can refer to the following tutorial to ensure that your CPU is SGX-supported.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.1 Run a Local Development Network</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/developer/run-a-local-development-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/developer/run-a-local-development-network/</guid>
      <description>Basic understanding of Linux shell and compiling is necessary to follow this tutorial.
 Overview In this tutorial, we are going to set up a &amp;quot;Hello World&amp;quot; development environment. We are going to deploy a full stack of the core blockchain and connect the Web UI to the blockchain. By the end of the tutorial, you will be able to:
 Send confidential transactions Get a ready-to-hack version of Phala Network for building your own confidential Dapps  A full Phala Network stack has three components plus a Web UI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.2 Hello World: your first confidential contract</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/developer/your-first-confidential-contract/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/developer/your-first-confidential-contract/</guid>
      <description>Basic understanding of Rust language programming and smart contract development knowledge is necessary to follow this tutorial.
 Overview In this tutorial, we are going to continue on the development environment we have set up in the previous chapter, and explore how a confidential smart contract is made. By the end of this tutorial, you will:
 Learn how to develop a confidential contract Interact with the contract from the Web UI Build your own confidential contract  For a high-level overview of Phala Network, please check the previous chapters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.2 Software Configuration</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/1-2-software-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/1-2-software-configuration/</guid>
      <description>System Requirement  This tutorial is based on Ubuntu 18.04. Ubuntu with versions other than 18.04 are not covered in this tutorial, though they and other Linux distributions may also work as well. How to install Ubuntu 18.04 Make sure all your packages are up-to-date:  1  sudo apt update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo apt upgrade -y &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo apt autoremove -y   Install Docker-CE Uninstall the older versions of Docker if they exist</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.3 Set Miner Stash</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/1-3-set-miner-stash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/1-3-set-miner-stash/</guid>
      <description>Connecting to Testnet Vendetta Open the Phala Network PoC-3 Web UI at: https://poc3.phala.network
Creating Phala Accounts You need to create two accounts: a stash account and a controller account. You may refer to this tutorial about how to create a single account.
Tip: to better manage your stash accounts and according controller accounts, we recommend to name an account pair with the same prefix. E.g.,
 Emily Stash / Emily Controller</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.3 Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/developer/troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/developer/troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description>phala-blockchain Probelm: &amp;quot;consider giving accuracy a type&amp;quot; when building substrate error[E0282]: type annotations needed --&amp;gt; .../substrate/primitives/arithmetic/src/fixed_point.rs:541:9 | 541 | let accuracy = P::ACCURACY.saturated_into(); | ^^^^^^^^ consider giving `accuracy` a type ... 1604 | / implement_fixed!( 1605 | | FixedI128, 1606 | | test_fixed_i128, 1607 | | i128, ... | 1611 | | [-170141183460469231731.687303715884105728, 170141183460469231731.687303715884105727]_&amp;quot;, 1612 | | ); | |__- in this macro invocation | = note: this error originates in a macro (in Nightly builds, run with -Z macro-backtrace for more info) This is a known issue caused by Rust nightly regression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2.1 Deploy the Full Stack</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/2-1-deploy-the-full-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/2-1-deploy-the-full-stack/</guid>
      <description>WARNING: Operations at this step may reset your previous Phala blockchain data and you will need to re-deploy the docker containers. For more detail, refer to our Dockerfile Github repo. You can find the latest Phala Network docker images from the official repo.
PLEASE follow the order of deploying the three docker containers below.
 Deploying Phala full-node A Phala full-node helps maintain the backbone of the network. We suggest you to run a Phala full-node on a device with 50+ GB storage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2.2 Set Commission</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/2-2-set-commission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/2-2-set-commission/</guid>
      <description>Go to Developer -&amp;gt; Extrinsics. Choose your Controller account -&amp;gt; phalaModule -&amp;gt; setPayoutPrefs(payout_comission, payout_target) Fill in commission (from 0 to 100) and choose the account where you want to receive the mining rewards at target.   The commission rate influences your final profits. For any mining reward you get, you always take the commission from it, and then distribute the rest propotionally to the mining stakers. For example, a comission of 100 means all the profits are tranferred to your specified account and a comission of 0 will share all the profits to your mining stakers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2.3 Veirfy the Miner State</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/2-3-verify-the-miner-state/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/2-3-verify-the-miner-state/</guid>
      <description>Go to Developer -&amp;gt; Chain state :
 Check miner score: phalaModule - &amp;gt;workerState -&amp;gt; choose your stash account  score.overallScore: the total points that a miner scores features: number of enabled cores, and the level of your cores（1-4）.   Check stash state: stashState Confirm the binding between stash and controller addresses: phalaModule.stash(controller) An example of all the details of mining state is shown below:  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3.1 Set Miner Stakes</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-1-set-miner-stakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-1-set-miner-stakes/</guid>
      <description>As designed in Phala Token Economics, each miner is required to stake at least 1620 PHA per core before mining starts. On testnet Vendetta, to better perform a stress test on Phala network and allow more miners to participate, Phala network will automatically stake for miners after they register.
However, to score a higher rank in the Miner Race, you can earn more points by using better hardwares, staking more tPHA, or simply running for a longer period, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3.2 Start Mining</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-2-start-mining/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-2-start-mining/</guid>
      <description> Go to Develoepr -&amp;gt; Extrinsics Choose your controller account，click phalaModule -&amp;gt; startMiningIntention() ，and Submit Transaction.  Then you will wait for the next mining period (every 1 hour) to get started.
Mining States Verification  Go to Developer → Chain State Click phalaModule → miningState Choose your stash account  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3.3 Stop Mining</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-3-stop-mining/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-3-stop-mining/</guid>
      <description> Go to Developer → Extrinsics Choose your controller account，clickphalaModule → stopMiningIntention() → Submit Transaction  Then you will wait for the next mining period (every 1 hour) to get stopped.
Miner State Verification  Go toDeveloper → Chain State phalaModule → workerState → Stash account phalaModule → miningState → Stash account  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3.4 Check Miner Profits</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-4-check-mining-profits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-4-check-mining-profits/</guid>
      <description> Go to Developer → Chain State Click phalaModule → fire(Accountld): BalanceOf  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3.5 Upgrade Miner</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-5-upgrade-miner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-5-upgrade-miner/</guid>
      <description>Stop Mining  If your miner is not in mining status, please start the upgrade from step 2.
   Refer to this link to stop mining.
  Wait until the end of the current mining period (1 hour per mining period). If you stop the miner too early, you may get slashed.
  Run the following commands to kill the original containers:
1 2 3  docker kill phala-phost docker kill phala-pruntime docker kill phala-node     Reset Docker Containers   Run the commands below to remove cached data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/4-faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/4-faq/</guid>
      <description>Get connected Please don&#39;t hesitate to ask us if you have any questions. You can find us at:
 Discord #miner channel: https://discord.gg/zjdJ7d844d Telegram miner group: https://t.me/phalaminer  Q: It says &amp;quot;no such command&amp;quot; after I typed docker pull docker.pkg.github.com/phala-network/phala-docker/phala-node:pre-test-4 Please check the installation of Docker-CE.
Q: It says &amp;quot;permission denied&amp;quot; Add sudo in front of your commands.
Q: How to check if my installed driver is SGX or DCAP  Run ls /dev/isgx and if the file exists: SGX-driver Run ls /dev/sgx and if the directory exists: DCAP-driver  Q: Where are the code releases / native build?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
