<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PoC-3 Vendetta Mining Guide on Phala Network Wiki</title>
    <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PoC-3 Vendetta Mining Guide on Phala Network Wiki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1.1 Hardware Requirement and Configuration</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/1-1-hardware-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/1-1-hardware-configuration/</guid>
      <description>Phala Network operates on trusted hardwares, in this case, Intel CPUs which support SGX feature. SGX was first introduced in 2015 with the sixth generation Intel Core microprocessors based on the Skylake microarchitecture. In practice, the support of SGX feature also relies on your motherboard and BIOS configurations. In this section, we will first ensure that necessary hardware requirements are satisfied and all your hardwares are correcly configured.
General Hardware Requirements CPU Requirement You can refer to the following tutorial to ensure that your CPU is SGX-supported.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.2 Software Configuration</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/1-2-software-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/1-2-software-configuration/</guid>
      <description>System Requirement  This tutorial is based on Ubuntu 18.04. Ubuntu with versions other than 18.04 are not covered in this tutorial, though they and other Linux distributions may also work as well. How to install Ubuntu 18.04 Make sure wget is installed all your packages are up-to-date:  1sudo apt update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo apt upgrade -y &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo apt autoremove -y 2sudo apt install wget Install Phala-solo-Scripts Download the Phala-solo-Scripts form Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.3 Set Miner Stash</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/1-3-set-miner-stash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/1-3-set-miner-stash/</guid>
      <description>Connecting to Testnet Vendetta Open the Phala Network PoC-3 Web UI at: https://poc3.phala.network
Creating Phala Accounts You need to create two accounts: a stash account and a controller account. You may refer to this tutorial about how to create a single account.
Tip: to better manage your stash accounts and according controller accounts, we recommend to name an account pair with the same prefix. E.g.,
 Emily Stash / Emily Controller</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.4 On-Chain Staking</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/1-4-on-chain-stake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/1-4-on-chain-stake/</guid>
      <description>Over Staking for Computing Task Process of Staking  Stake Transfer to your stash account, nominator your or other miner, the token will be locked in this round and become effective in next round. Withdraw Stake The token will be pre-unlocked, and be unlocked in next round.  How to Operating  Ready to work  Open the following two pages and select the corresponding transaction or query
 Select the stath account，select “miningStaking” in &amp;quot;submit the following extrinsic&amp;quot;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.5 Introduction of 1605 Race Privacy Computing Task</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/1-5-introduction-of-1605-race-privacy-computing-task/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/1-5-introduction-of-1605-race-privacy-computing-task/</guid>
      <description>Introduction of 1605 Race Privacy Computing Task Who are familiar with Phala Tokenomics know that Phala&#39;s mining rewards are divided into online rewards and computing task rewards. In this 1605 Race V2, on the basis of online rewards, the emphasis is on the introduction of computing task rewards. This article is an introduction to the computing tasks of the Vendetta testnet.
Background summary  The computing tasks in this testnet are generated virtually by the system, and 5 computing tasks are fixed for each Round (600 blocks).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2.1 Start the Phala miner</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/2-1-start-the-phala-miner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/2-1-start-the-phala-miner/</guid>
      <description>Start the Phala miner 1sudo phala start  The scripts will run for a long time.The pruntime and phost will start until the full node got the highest block.
 It costs a tiny amount of tPHA as well. Before deploying pHost, please make sure there are a certain amount of tPHA in your Stash account and controller account. Click here to learn how to obtain tPHA.
Check the phala miner status You can check your miner status as this command：</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2.2 Set Commission</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/2-2-set-commission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/2-2-set-commission/</guid>
      <description>Go to Developer -&amp;gt; Extrinsics. Choose your Controller account -&amp;gt; phalaModule -&amp;gt; setPayoutPrefs(payout_comission, payout_target) Fill in commission (from 0 to 100) and choose the account where you want to receive the mining rewards at target.   The commission rate influences your final profits. For any mining reward you get, you always take the commission from it, and then distribute the rest propotionally to the mining stakers. For example, a comission of 100 means all the profits are tranferred to your specified account and a comission of 0 will share all the profits to your mining stakers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2.3 Veirfy the Miner State</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/2-3-verify-the-miner-state/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/2-3-verify-the-miner-state/</guid>
      <description>Go to Developer -&amp;gt; Chain state :
 Check miner score: phalaModule - &amp;gt;workerState -&amp;gt; choose your stash account  score.overallScore: the total points that a miner scores features: number of enabled cores, and the level of your cores（1-4）.   Check stash state: stashState Confirm the binding between stash and controller addresses: phalaModule.stash(controller) An example of all the details of mining state is shown below:  Mining State References  Empty: A rare tag to see if you have registered your miner successfully Free: Your miner is successfully registered but haven&#39;t start mining Gatekeeper: Your Gatekeeper role is enabled MiningPending: Your miner will start mining in the next round Mining: BlockNumber: Your miner is mining; the number aside is the blockheight where you start MiningStopping: Your miner will stop mining in the next round (state changed into Free).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3.1 Set Miner Stakes</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-1-set-miner-stakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-1-set-miner-stakes/</guid>
      <description>As designed in Phala Token Economics, each miner is required to stake at least 1620 PHA per core before mining starts. On testnet Vendetta, to better perform a stress test on Phala network and allow more miners to participate, Phala network will automatically stake for miners after they register.
However, to score a higher rank in the Miner Race, you can earn more points by using better hardwares, staking more tPHA, or simply running for a longer period, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3.2 Start Mining</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-2-start-mining/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-2-start-mining/</guid>
      <description>Go to Develoepr -&amp;gt; Extrinsics Choose your controller account，click phalaModule -&amp;gt; startMiningIntention() ，and Submit Transaction.  Then you will wait for the next mining period (every 1 hour) to get started.
Mining States Verification  Go to Developer → Chain State Choose phalaModule → workerState, and choose your stash account If there&#39;s a Mining with block height after state, congratulations, your miner is working. If there&#39;s a Miningpending, it means your miner will start mining from the next round (600 blocks later).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3.3 Stop Mining</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-3-stop-mining/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-3-stop-mining/</guid>
      <description>Go to Developer → Extrinsics Choose your controller account，clickphalaModule → stopMiningIntention() → Submit Transaction  Then you will wait for the next mining period (every 1 hour) to get stopped.
Miner State Verification onchain  Go toDeveloper → Chain State phalaModule → workerState → Stash account phalaModule → miningState → Stash account  Miner State Verification 1sudo phala status Stop the Phala miner You can stop your phala miner as this command:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3.4 Check Miner Profits</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-4-check-mining-profits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-4-check-mining-profits/</guid>
      <description> Go to Developer → Chain State Click phalaModule → fire(Accountld): BalanceOf  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3.5 Upgrade Miner</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-5-upgrade-miner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/3-5-upgrade-miner/</guid>
      <description>Stop mining  If your miner is not in mining status, feel free to skip this step.
   Refer to this link to stop mining.
  Wait until the end of the current mining period (1 hour per mining period). If you stop the miner too early, you may get slashed.
  Run the following commands to kill the original containers:
1sudo phala stop   Update the Phala miner and clean the local files Run the commands below to remove cached data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/4-faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/4-faq/</guid>
      <description>Miner Community Please don&#39;t hesitate to ask us if you have any questions. You can find us at:

I. Glossary  SGX. Software Guard Extensions. TEE. Trusted Execution Environment. Full-node. A full node is pruned, meaning it discards all information older than 256 blocks, but keeps the extrinsics for all past blocks, and the genesis block. A node that is pruned this way requires much less space than an archive node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4.1 Error References</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/4.1-error-references/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/poc3/4.1-error-references/</guid>
      <description>Error How to Fix     No genesis block Please upgrade your miner node following these steps.   Failed to decode signature Please kindly check whether your node has finished syncing.   FailedToCallRegisterWorker You may refer to:
1. Go to https://telemetry.polkadot.io/#list/Phala%20PoC-3 and check whether your node has finished sycning;
2. type in sudo docker attach --sig-proxy=false --detach-keys=ctrl-c phala-pruntime to learn whether your pRuntime has been launched</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
