<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Governance on Phala Network Wiki</title>
    <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/governance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Governance on Phala Network Wiki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/governance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1 Participate in Democracy</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/governance/1-participate-in-democracy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/governance/1-participate-in-democracy/</guid>
      <description>Participate in Democracy The public referenda chamber is one of the three bodies of on-chain governance as it&amp;rsquo;s instantiated in Phala and Khala. The other two bodies are the council and the technical committee.
Public referenda can be proposed and voted on by any token holder in the system as long as they provide a bond. After a proposal is made, others can agree with it by seconding it and putting up tokens equal to the original bond.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Join the Council</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/governance/2-join-the-council/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/governance/2-join-the-council/</guid>
      <description>The council is an elected body of on-chain accounts that are intended to represent the passive stakeholders of Phala and/or Khala. The council has two major tasks in governance: proposing referenda and vetoing dangerous or malicious referenda. For more information on the council, see the governance page. This guide will walk you through entering your candidacy to the council.
Submit Candidacy Submitting your candidacy for the council requires a small bond of PHA / K-PHA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Voting for Councillors</title>
      <link>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/governance/3-voting-for-councillors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wiki.phala.network/en-us/docs/governance/3-voting-for-councillors/</guid>
      <description>The council is an elected body of on-chain accounts that are intended to represent the passive stakeholders of Phala and/or Khala. The council has two major tasks in governance: proposing referenda and vetoing dangerous or malicious referenda. For more information on the council, see the Governance page. This guide will walk you through voting for councillors in the elections.
Voting for Councillors Voting for councillors requires you to lock 5 PHA on Phala or 5 K-PHA on Khala for the duration of your vote.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
